There really is a hidden dragon and a crouching tiger in my brother's house.
형 집에는 정말 숨은 용과 웅크리고 있는 호랑이가 있다.
A female messenger can play music like this
여자 메신저가 이런 음악을 틀 수 있구나
It's breathtaking
아슬아슬하다
We looked at musicians in the city's music studios.
도시의 음악 스튜디오에서 음악가들을 살펴보았습니다.
It's in a place that can't be reached
다 닿을 수 없는 곳에 있어
I think it's average
내 생각엔 평균인 것 같아
Because I think that’s natural
형은 그게 당연하다고 생각하니까
Why don't you hand her over to me?
그녀를 나에게 넘겨주는 게 어때?
My mother loves music theory.
우리 어머니는 음악이론을 아주 좋아하세요.
I gave him to her to relieve her boredom.
나는 그녀의 지루함을 덜어주기 위해 그를 그녀에게주었습니다.
sister-in-law
시누이
what's the problem?
뭐가 문제 야?
The landlady is calling.
집주인 아주머니께서 전화하십니다.
What are you giggling at?
뭘 보고 낄낄거리는 거야?
landlord's sin
집주인 죄
The sound of Mu Yao's piano felt so good right now.
지금 무야오의 피아노 소리가 너무 기분 좋았어요.
I was instantly fascinated.
순간 매료됐어요
I didn't hear the head of the household's question.
나는 가장의 질문을 듣지 못했습니다.
Just now I said that this Zhongzhai is really full of hidden dragons and crouching tigers.
방금 나는이 Zhongzhai에는 정말로 숨겨진 용과 웅크린 호랑이가 가득하다고 말했습니다.
The sound of a woman playing the piano is so special.
여자가 피아노치는 소리가 너무 특별해요
I heard that my sister-in-law's piano skills are also the best in Hwangcheong.
형수님의 피아노 실력도 황청에서 최고라고 들었습니다.
I don’t know how it compares?
비교하면 어떤지 모르겠는데?
what?
무엇?
A Qian's piano skills were learned from famous masters.
A Qian의 피아노 기술은 유명한 거장들로부터 배웠습니다.
- Nature is rare in the world - isn't it?
- 자연은 세상에 드물죠 - 그렇죠?
Will I have the honor of hearing the song today?
오늘 노래를 들을 수 있는 영광이 있을까 ?
Muyao Zhuyu is in front.
Muyao Zhuyu가 앞에 있습니다.
I'm ashamed of myself
내 자신이 부끄럽다
The senior just said
선배가 방금 말했어
Daughter-in-law, don’t look down on yourself.
며느리, 자신을 얕보지 마세요
Other days I can listen to the piano
다른 날에는 피아노를 들을 수 있어요
Today is my uncle's birthday.
오늘은 삼촌 생일이에요
I think it would be better to stay out of the spotlight.
스포트라이트를 받지 않는 게 좋을 것 같아요.
Put the piano away
피아노를 치워두세요
yes
예
Because my sister-in-law considers my brother’s birthday very important,
형수님이 형님 생일을 너무 중요하게 여기시니까,
You must have prepared a truly amazing birthday present, right?
정말 놀라운 생일 선물을 준비하셨겠죠 ?
I'm not...
나는 아니에요‥
No wonder I have been in Zhongshi Garden before.
내가 전에 Zhongshi Garden에 있었던 것도 당연합니다.
My brother is so anxious to come back.
형은 너무 돌아오고 싶어 안달이 나
My sister-in-law didn't even think about showing off her superb piano skills .
형수는 자신의 최고의 피아노 실력을 자랑할 생각 조차 하지 않았습니다.
This birthday present is definitely not ordinary.
이번 생일선물은 확실히 평범하지 않네요
Teacher, please wait a moment.
선생님, 잠시만 기다려주세요.
I'll be back as soon as I go, Qian Zhi
가자마자 돌아올게요, Qian Zhi
Why did that woman suddenly ask Mu Yao to perform?
왜 그 여자가 갑자기 Mu Yao에게 공연을 요청 했나요?
It turns out I was ready for something else.
나는 다른 것을 준비한 것으로 밝혀졌습니다.
What should I prepare?
무엇을 준비해야 할까요?
How did I know that they would still think of me after hearing Mu Yao play the piano?
Mu Yao가 피아노를 연주하는 것을 듣고도 그들이 여전히 나를 생각할 것이라는 것을 어떻게 알았습니까 ?
I can only treat a dead horse as a living doctor.
나는 죽은 말을 살아 있는 의사로서만 치료할 수 있다.
The big lady is back
큰 아줌마가 돌아왔다
On birthdays, it is customary to have a birthday soup cake.
생일에는 생일 수프 케이크를 먹는 것이 관례입니다.
I just happened to see my uncle not moving his chopsticks very much.
방금 삼촌이 젓가락을 별로 움직이지 않는 걸 우연히 봤어요.
So I dedicate this soup cake to my uncle.
그래서 나는 이 수프 케이크를 삼촌에게 바칩니다.
I hope you don't hate it
싫어하지 않으셨으면 좋겠습니다
Manners are light, but affection is heavy.
예의는 가벼우나 애정은 무거워
are you interested
당신은 관심이 있습니다
I heard
나는 들었다
The Hua family's daughter has been pampered since childhood.
Hua 가족의 딸은 어린 시절부터 애지중지했습니다.
These ten fingers do not touch the spring water
이 열 손가락은 샘물에 닿지 않는다
When did your sister-in-law learn these cooking skills?
형수는 언제 이런 요리 기술을 배웠나요?
I learned this privately and secretly
나는 이것을 사적으로 비밀리에 배웠다
I want to give you a surprise gift
깜짝 선물을 주고 싶어
I had no idea that the skills I learned in exile would lead to something like this.
유배지에서 배운 기술이 이렇게 될 줄은 몰랐습니다
He reassured me again and again
그는 나를 몇 번이고 안심시켜 주었어요
But the sound of Mu Yao’s piano
그런데 무야오의 피아노 소리는
Why didn't a tit-for-tat showdown occur between Jong Ye-ran and Jong Hee-woo?
종예란과 종희우 사이에 티격태격 대결이 발생하지 않은 이유는 무엇입니까 ?
Is it because you don't have my support?
내 지원이 없기 때문입니까?
Can't she show her excellence?
그녀는 자신의 우수성을 보여줄 수 없습니까?
Why didn't you go......
왜 안 갔어 ......
It's hard to come here, senior.
여기 오기 힘든데 선배님
I'll be here a little longer
난 여기 좀 더 있을게요
Sir, you don’t think I’m bothering you, do you?
선배님, 제가 귀찮게 한다고 생각하지 않으실 거죠?
Of course not
당연히 아니지
Speaking of these days, I will report it to the store below.
요즘 말하면 아래 가게에보고하겠습니다.
There are always crafty people inquiring about Jiayin Menggui Dan's incense techniques .
Jiayin Menggui Dan의 향 기술 에 대해 문의하는 교활한 사람들이 항상 있습니다 .
I don't know which faction it comes from.
어느 세력 출신인지는 모르겠습니다.
quite uneasy
상당히 불안하다
Every year, Cain's dream returns to Dan.
매년 가인의 꿈이 단에게 돌아옵니다
It's all done with your hands.
그것은 모두 당신의 손으로 이루어집니다.
No one has ever seen it
한번도 본 사람은 없어요
This is an exclusive secret passed down from the ancestors of the Zhong family.
이것은 중씨 가문의 조상들로부터 전해 내려온 독점적인 비법입니다.
It's normal for some people to want to pry.
일부 사람들이 캐고 싶어하는 것은 정상입니다.
So the head of the household
그래서 가장은
Do not worry too much
너무 걱정하지 마세요
After all, the Ge family was once good at cheating.
결국 Ge 가족은 한때 바람을 피우는 데 능숙했습니다.
I've never been able to imitate
난 한번도 흉내낼 수 없었어
It’s not a bad idea to ask questions on a regular basis.
평소에 문의해 보시는 것도 나쁘지 않습니다.
Only two stores, one north and one south, knew it.
단지 북쪽과 남쪽의 두 가게가 그것을 알고 있었을 뿐입니다.
Probably not an ordinary person
아마 보통 사람은 아니겠지
However, my older brother lived in the south.
그런데, 형은 남쪽에 살았었어요.
There should be a map of the southern cities here, right?
여기 남부 도시의 지도가 있어야겠죠?
Now is the time to take it out and study it together.
이제 꺼내서 같이 공부할 시간이에요.
- Southern store situation - OK
- 남부 매장 상황 - OK
The map is in my study.
지도는 내 서재에 있어요
I'll get it right now
지금 당장 가져올게요
What are you thinking, daughter-in-law?
무슨 생각해요, 며느리님?
I'm so ecstatic
너무 황홀해
Where is your uncle?
삼촌은 어디 계시나요?
I just told my brother about the stores down south.
방금 형한테 남쪽에 있는 가게들에 대해 얘기했어요.
He went to the study to get a map of the city.
그는 도시 지도를 가지러 서재에 갔다
come back later
나중에 다시 오세요
I guess what I said to my brother was really meaningless.
제가 형에게 한 말은 정말 의미가 없는 것 같습니다.
That's why you've lost your mind.
그렇기 때문에 당신은 정신을 잃었습니다.
I'm the fool
바보는 나야
I don't understand what the head of the family and my uncle are talking about about business.
가장과 삼촌이 사업에 대해 무슨 말을하는지 이해가 안됩니다.
I also ask for forgiveness from the owner.
주인에게도 용서를 구합니다.
Once, when Huadu Guan interceded for the Mu family,
한때 화도관(Huadu Guan)이 무(Mu) 가문을 위해 중재했을 때,
When it comes to the store in the north, he seems to know everything about it.
북쪽의 상점에 관해서라면 그는 그 가게에 대해 모든 것을 알고 있는 것 같다.
I thought my sister-in-law was Gwanhwado’s daughter.
형수가 관화도의 딸인줄 알았는데
You should also be interested in stores in the South.
남부의 상점에도 관심이 있어야 합니다.
The landlord got it wrong.
집주인이 잘못 생각했어요
My sister-in-law thinks this is in Zhongzhai.
형수는 이곳이 Zhongzhai에 있다고 생각합니다
Are you confident to speak up?
말할 자신이 있나요?
I don't understand what the owner is saying.
주인이 무슨 말인지 이해가 안가네요
Are you Hua Qian?
Hua Qian입니까?
Throw away trivial thoughts
사소한 생각은 버려라
I don't think I can do anything if the head of the household is here.
가장이 여기 있으면 아무것도 할 수 없을 것 같아요
If you tell that person your identity
그 사람에게 당신의 정체를 알려준다면
Then there is only one fate for you
그렇다면 당신의 운명은 하나뿐이다
expelled from the city
도시에서 추방됨
you think too much
당신은 너무 많이 생각
What can I do now?
내가 지금 무엇을 할 수 있을까?
You don't even believe me
너조차 내 말을 믿지 않잖아
How can I expect the head of a family I’ve only met once to trust me?
딱 한 번 만난 가장이 감히 나를 믿을 것이라고 기대할 수 있겠는가 ?
Achen will never do as you say.
아첸은 절대 네 말대로 안 할 거야
It's you who's blinded by hate
증오에 눈이 먼 건 너야
I can't see the facts clearly.
나는 사실을 명확하게 볼 수 없습니다.
yes
예
Your Hua Qian is meek, pure, and ignorant of worldly affairs.
당신의 Hua Qian은 온유하고 순수하며 세상사에 무지합니다.
she never designed me
그녀는 나를 디자인한 적이 없어
I did not have my father imprisoned or exiled.
나는 내 아버지를 감옥에 가두거나 유배시키도록 하지 않았습니다.
But Jong Ye-ran
하지만 종예란은
Do you really think I'm a random biter?
내가 정말 아무렇게나 물어뜯는 사람이라고 생각하는가?
How many times have I said this?
내가 몇 번이나 말했지?
I never want to hear this again
다시는 이런 말을 듣고 싶지 않아요
I never took the initiative to ask you
난 솔선해서 너한테 물어본 적 없어
You are the one who felt guilty and committed the crime yourself.
죄책감을 갖고 스스로 범죄를 저지른 것은 바로 당신이다
keeps asking me questions
나에게 계속해서 질문을 던진다
Obviously don't take my word for it
분명히 내 말을 믿지 마세요
I'm sure it would hurt her if she found out.
분명히 알면 그녀에게 상처를 줄 거야
Why did you abandon Hua Qian on the wedding night and on the way home?
왜 결혼식 날 밤 과 집으로 가는 길 에 Hua Qian을 버렸나요 ?
You're willing to risk that much to save me?
나를 구하기 위해 그렇게 큰 위험을 감수한다고요?
Nakaya Ake
나카야 아케
Who is it between us?
우리 사이에 누구야?
Can't you see your own mind?
자신의 마음을 제대로 볼 수 없나요?
Of course I am Hua Qian
물론 나는 Hua Qian이다
As far as I know, Hua Qian
내가 아는 한 Hua Qian
She could never see any other women around her brother.
그녀는 오빠 주변에 다른 여자를 전혀 볼 수 없었습니다 .
needless to mention
언급 할 필요없는
The act of listening to requests from other women in front of one's older brother.
형 앞에서 다른 여자들의 부탁을 들어주는 행위
I think I once said this to my head of the household.
예전에 가장에게도 이런 말을 한 적이 있었던 것 같습니다.
Being a woman and being a wife are inherently different.
여자가 되는 것과 아내가 되는 것은 본질적으로 다르다
Please explain in detail and listen.
자세히 설명하고 들어주세요
When I was a kid
어렸을 때
My parents are half of my sky
부모님은 내 하늘의 반
Of course I have nothing to worry about.
물론 나는 걱정할 게 없다.
Looking at just one person
한 사람만 바라보며
Because my uncle is the only person in my life
내 인생에 삼촌은 유일한 사람이니까
So I do whatever I can
그래서 난 웬만하면 뭐든지 해
I also see in his eyes
나는 또한 그의 눈에
I'm the only one left
나만 남았어
What I learned after getting married
결혼하고 나서 알게 된 사실
I have to last all day
하루종일 버텨야 해
Don't look at everything from only one side
모든 일을 한쪽 면만 보지 말고
So I still love my uncle
그래서 나는 아직도 삼촌을 사랑하지만
But you can't accept him as yours like you used to
하지만 예전처럼 그를 네 것으로 받아들일 수는 없어
That's because I love him so much
그건 바로 내가 그 사람을 너무 사랑하기 때문이야
Then I really understood
그제서야 난 정말 이해하게 됐어
If that person is happy
그 사람이 행복하다면
I am willing to do anything.
나는 무엇이든 할 의향이 있다
your confession
너의 고백
I'm really jealous
정말 부럽다
Senior, are you still moved after hearing this?
선배님, 이 말을 듣고 아직도 감동이 드시나요?
-You... -The slave said something nonsense.
-너는‥ -노예가 말도 안되는 소리를 했어
I'm really embarrassed
정말 부끄러워요
- Qian Zhi - Madam
- Qian Zhi - 부인
attentive‥
주의 깊은‥
-Chenji, close the door quickly . -Okay.
-첸지, 빨리 문 닫아 -알았어
oppa style
오빠 스타일
It was always out of my reach
언제나 내 손이 닿지 않는 곳에 있었어
Thank you, brother.
고마워요, 형제님
- Madam, please wait for me. - Madam, you woke up early today.
- 부인, 저를 기다려주세요. - 부인, 오늘 일찍 일어나셨어요
What is this, what does it do?
이게 뭐야, 이게 무슨 일을 하는 거야?
I've been married for a while and now it's time to go back to see my parents.
결혼한 지 꽤 되어서 이제 부모님을 만나러 돌아갈 시간이 되었습니다.
Why do you suddenly want to leave?
갑자기 왜 떠나고 싶어?
Have you ever sent a letter to Huaihai?
화자이에게 편지를 보낸 적이 있나요?
If you don't lose face, you will lose face.
체면을 잃지 않으면 체면을 잃게 됩니다.
Madam, please wait for me.
부인, 저를 기다려주세요
Madam, what's going on?
부인, 무슨 일이에요?
Mother Li, it’s better to ask someone else.
리 어머니, 다른 사람에게 물어보는 것이 낫습니다.
I'm going to chase after the eldest lady.
큰아줌마를 쫓아갈 거야
Madam, please wait for me.
부인, 저를 기다려주세요
oldest woman
가장 나이 많은 여자
uncle
삼촌
The subordinate just saw the eldest aunt packing her things and returning to the mansion.
부하는 방금 큰아줌마가 짐을 싸서 저택으로 돌아가는 것을 보았습니다.
Why don’t you go find your eldest sister?
맏언니를 찾으러 가지 않겠습니까?
I'm not going
안 가요
yes
예
Hoegaju
회가주
maid next to uncle
삼촌 옆에 하녀
She is actually the daughter of the convicted Mu Yunping.
그녀는 실제로 유죄 판결을 받은 무윈핑(Mu Yunping)의 딸입니다.
His father has already left Beijing
그의 아버지는 이미 베이징을 떠났다
She was the only one left in Zhongzhai.
그녀는 Zhongzhai에 남은 유일한 사람이었습니다.
never leave
결코 떠나지
- Does the senior know her identity? - Spy's Report
- 선배는 그녀의 정체를 알고 있나요? - 스파이의 보고
Before my uncle got married
삼촌이 결혼하기 전에
He formed a personal relationship with the daughter of the Mu family.
무 가문의 딸과 사적인 관계를 맺었다
I need to know who she is
그녀의 정체를 알아야 해
I know my brother’s personality best.
형의 성격은 내가 제일 잘 안다.
He always treats single girls without pretense.
그는 항상 미혼 소녀들을 가식없이 대합니다.
Because we had a personal relationship
우리는 개인적인 관계를 가졌기 때문에
Maybe the relationship needs to change.
아마 관계가 달라져야 할 것 같아요
However, the uncle did not intervene in the Mu family's case.
그러나 삼촌은 무씨 일가의 사건에 개입하지 않았다.
In this case, he just accepted the legitimate daughter of the Mu family.
이번 경우에는 무 가문의 적녀를 받아들였을 뿐입니다.
Of course, my brother cannot be related to the Ge family by blood.
물론 형은 게씨 가문과 혈연관계가 있을 수 없다.
After all, he was probably the person the Ge family hated the most at the time.
결국 그는 당시 게씨 가문이 가장 미워했던 인물이었을 것이다.
He was responsible for all of the Zhong family's businesses in the south.
그는 남쪽에서 Zhong 가족의 모든 사업을 책임졌습니다.
Because he was able to delegate power to the Meng family without any hesitation.
그는 아무런 주저함 없이 맹씨 가문에 권력을 위임할 수 있었기 때문에
Then that person is not power-hungry.
그렇다면 그 사람은 권력에 굶주린 사람이 아니다.
But now his unusual behavior
하지만 이제 그의 특이한 행동은
I'm afraid of that.
나는 그것이 두렵다.
Affection
애정
Does Hua Qian know the identity of the Mu family girl?
Hua Qian은 Mu 가족 소녀의 정체를 알고 있습니까?
Before the eldest wife left the cabinet,
큰 부인이 내각을 떠나기 전에,
She is very close to the direct daughter of the Mu family.
그녀는 Mu 가족의 직계 딸과 매우 가깝습니다.
Then that person is really...
그럼 그 사람은 정말 ......
How generous.
얼마나 관대한지
House owner
집주인
Should we send more manpower?
인력을 더 보내야 하나?
Are you looking at Zhong Zhai?
종자이(Zhong Zhai)를 쳐다보고 있나요?
But I always feel like something's wrong
하지만 항상 뭔가 잘못된 것 같은 느낌이 들어요
He did not hesitate to take medication to achieve his goals.
그는 자신의 목표를 달성하기 위해 서슴지 않고 약을 복용했다.
Why have I suddenly become so generous now that I'm married?
결혼한 지금 갑자기 왜 이렇게 관대해졌나요?
Please do not make any announcements about what we reported today.
오늘 보고한 내용에 대해 어떤 발표도 하지 마세요.
There is no need to specifically order people to watch Zhong Zhai.
Zhong Zhai를 감시하도록 특별히 사람들에게 명령할 필요는 없습니다.
Self-theft case while in custody of the Mu family
뮤 일가 구금 중 자기도둑질 사건
Just do it the way it's supposed to be done
그냥 정해진 대로 처리해
If there's another secret
또 다른 비밀이 있다면
The person behind this will definitely make another move
이 뒤에 있는 사람은 분명 또 다른 움직임을 보일 거야
Yes, he is the head of the family.
응, 가장이야
younger sister
여동생
Dad mom
아빠 엄마
Sister, why did you come alone?
언니, 왜 혼자 오셨어요?
I haven't been home for a long time
오랫동안 집에 없었어요
I miss my father and mother very much.
나는 아버지와 어머니가 매우 그리워요.
So I decided to just come back and stay for a few days.
그래서 그냥 돌아와서 며칠 동안 머물기로 결정했습니다.
Okay, now I finally have someone to talk to.
좋아, 이제 드디어 얘기할 사람이 생겼어.
Sister, you...
언니, 당신은 ‥
Qian Er
치엔얼
you
너
Did you have a conflict with your uncle?
삼촌과 갈등이 있었나요?
How can you do that? I just want to go home.
어떻게 그럴 수가 있어 그냥 집에 가고 싶어
nonsense
무의미한 말
It's been so long since I got married
결혼한지 너무 오래됐어
He still has a childlike personality.
아직도 어린아이 같은 성격을 가지고 있어요
uncle
삼촌
Qian Er
치엔얼
You are now Zhongzhai's eldest son
당신은 이제 Zhongzhai의 장남입니다
when you get married
당신이 결혼할 때
Have you forgotten what your father and mother told you?
네 아버지와 어머니가 네게 한 말을 잊었느냐?
marry as wife
아내로 결혼하다
You can't be like that girl's family.
그 소녀의 가족처럼 될 수는 없습니다.
This is a mess
이건 난리야
It's not right to just run to your parents' house.
그냥 부모님 집으로 달려가는 것은 옳지 않습니다.
I'm not really mad at my uncle
난 정말 삼촌한테 화를 내지 않았어
I just want to go home and stay for a few days.
그냥 집에 가서 며칠만 머물고 싶어요
-This... -You...
-이것‥ - 당신은‥
He said he had only been married for two months.
결혼한 지 두 달밖에 안 됐다고 하더군요.
Just run to your parents house.
그냥 부모님 집으로 달려가세요
What will this look like if it spreads?
이것이 퍼지면 어떤 모습이 될까요?
How do you want others to view you, uncle?
다른 사람들이 당신을 어떻게 보길 바라나요, 삼촌?
What do you think of our Hua family?
우리 Hua 가족에 대해 어떻게 생각하시나요?
i can tell you
난 너에게 말할 수있어
I'll take you back after dinner at the latest.
늦어도 저녁식사 후에는 다시 데려다줄게
If you have any complaints or conflicts, please state them clearly in front of me and my uncle.
불만이나 갈등이 있으면 저와 삼촌 앞에서 명확하게 말해주세요.
so that I can give you justice
내가 당신에게 정의를 내릴 수 있도록
I don’t need it, father.
필요없어요 아버지
It's really okay
정말 괜찮아요
is it so
그래요
It was just a last minute idea.
그것은 단지 마지막 순간의 아이디어였습니다.
good
좋은
If what uncle says is right
삼촌 말이 맞다면
You shouldn't cause trouble by force.
무리하게 문제를 일으키면 안 돼요
In those days, if you wanted to live or die, you had to marry her.
그 당시에는 살고 죽으려면 그녀와 결혼해야 했습니다.
I went right back without even eating dinner.
저녁도 안먹고 바로 돌아가
Qian Er
치엔얼
I need to change my mood
기분을 바꿔야 해
Did you forget what mom said?
엄마가 한 말을 잊었나요?
You are now Zhongzhai's eldest son
당신은 이제 Zhongzhai의 장남입니다
But I can take a concubine at any time.
하지만 나는 언제든지 첩을 데려갈 수 있어요.
As a newlywed, you run to your parents' house.
신혼이 되어 부모님 집으로 달려가게 됩니다.
Will you hear it if it goes viral?
널리 퍼지면 들리나요?
How many older ladies are waiting to sort out your gossip ?
당신의 가십을 정리하기 위해 몇 명의 나이 많은 숙녀분들이 기다리고 있습니까?
By then, my uncle's face will have disappeared.
그때쯤이면 삼촌의 얼굴이 사라질 거야
Will it make you feel better?
기분이 나아질까요?
I just went back to my parents' house.
방금 부모님 집으로 돌아갔어요
Why are the words coming out of Mom’s mouth so serious?
엄마 입에서 나오는 말이 왜 이렇게 심각해 ?
What Mom Just Said
방금 엄마가 한 말
Are you really thinking about me?
정말로 내 생각을 하고 있는 거야?
you‥
너‥
Qian'er was still praising your stability.
Qian'er는 여전히 당신의 안정을 칭찬하고 있었습니다
Now I'm acting like a child again
이제 난 또 어린애처럼 행동하고 있어
That uncle is a really popular person.
그 삼촌은 정말 인기가 많은 인물이에요
You put your uncle first in everything, right?
넌 모든 일에 있어서 삼촌을 최우선으로 생각하는구나, 그렇지?
It's not that Mom and Dad don't want you coming back.
아빠 엄마가 네가 돌아오는 걸 싫어하는 건 아니야
But you, newlywed, just ran home.
그런데 신혼인 당신은 방금 집으로 달려갔어요
Who wants to feel better and not think about it more?
누가 기분이 나아지고 그것에 대해 더 생각하지 않겠습니까?
good boy
착한 소년
Think carefully about what your mom said.
엄마가 한 말 잘 생각해봐
Don't be stubborn
고집 부리지 마세요
I'm going to meet your father
난 네 아버지를 만나러 갈 거야
Don't send anyone to look for your uncle.
삼촌을 찾으러 사람을 보내지 마세요.
It's just a matter between you two.
그건 단지 너희 둘 사이의 문제일 뿐이야.
Still, you have to figure it out yourself.
그래도 스스로 해결해야 해
- Please advise my sister . - Okay...
- 여동생에게 조언해주세요 - 알았어 ‥
-Sister, did you really fight with your uncle? -no‥
-언니, 정말 삼촌이랑 싸웠어요? -아니요‥
How many times do you want me to say that?
내가 몇 번이나 말하길 바라나요?
regret
유감
I feel bad
기분이 안 좋아
I want to be alone for a while
한동안 혼자 있고 싶어
The eldest lady is just in a bad mood.
큰아줌마는 그냥 기분이 안 좋은 것뿐이야
I'm not really angry
별로 화난 건 아니야
Dalrangjun, eat some candied fruit.
달랑준아, 설탕에 절인 과일 좀 먹어
Being angry is good
화를 내는 것은 좋은 일이다
I won't worry if you get angry
화내면 걱정 안 할게
She was bullied outside.
그녀는 밖에서 괴롭힘을 당했다
What happened to the eldest lady?
가장 큰 부인에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
Is the eldest lady still sad because she got scolded by her boss?
큰아줌마는 상사에게 혼나서 아직도 슬퍼하고 있나요?
Actually, he's worried about you too.
사실 그 사람도 당신을 걱정하고 있어요
Tell me why my parents are so worried
우리 부모님이 왜 그렇게 걱정하는지 말해봐
What is my relationship with my uncle?
나와 삼촌의 관계는?
people like uncles
삼촌 같은 사람들
How many girls are there in the city competing for who to marry?
도시에는 결혼할 사람을 두고 경쟁하는 소녀가 몇 명이나 됩니까?
Du Guan and his wife also cherish the great man.
Du Guan과 그의 아내도 위대한 사람을 소중히 여깁니다.
So, if I take the initiative now and say
그러니까 지금 내가 솔선해서 말한다면
I don't want to choose Jong Ye-ran this time.
이번에는 종예란을 선택하고 싶지 않아요
It's absolutely impossible for those people to support it, right?
그 사람들이 지지하는 건 절대 불가능하잖아요?
Why not choose your uncle?
삼촌을 선택하는 게 어때요?
naught
아무것도 아님
It was originally about family.
원래는 가족 얘기였는데
I didn't have much hope
별로 희망이 없었는데
Just make it clear to me today
오늘은 나한테만 분명히 해줘
But whether it's my past life or this life
하지만 전생이든 이번 생이든
I've always fought alone
난 항상 혼자 싸워왔어
What is your past and present life?
과거와 현재의 삶은 무엇입니까?
Besides, how could the eldest aunt be alone?
게다가 어떻게 큰아줌마가 혼자일 수 있겠어요?
Du Guan and his wife are still here
Du Guan과 그의 아내는 아직 여기에 있습니다
Now my uncle also values ​​you very much.
이제 삼촌도 당신을 매우 소중하게 생각합니다
There is no one more perfect in the world than my eldest aunt.
세상에 큰아줌마보다 더 완벽한 사람은 없습니다.
The eldest lady doesn’t know.
큰아줌마는 몰라
This is the home of a girl who has not yet come out of Hwangseong Palace.
이곳은 황성궁에서 아직 나오지 않은 소녀의 집이다.
Everyone envies the eldest aunt.
다들 큰아줌마를 부러워해요
-Envy me? -yes
-나를 부러워하다? -예
The eldest lady did not notice this fact during each banquet.
큰 아줌마는 연회 때마다 그 사실을 눈치채지 못했다.
When the girls saw the eldest lady,
그 소녀들이 가장 큰 부인을 보았을 때,
Are your eyes red?
눈이 빨개졌나요?
oldest woman
가장 나이 많은 여자
Everything the slave said is true
노예가 말한 것은 모두 사실이다
Water thrown by a married daughter
결혼한 딸이 던진 물
Originally I was thinking of doing it again.
원래는 다시 해볼 생각이었는데
everything will get better
모든 게 좋아질 거야
Now it seems
이제는 것 같다
this is my fault
이건 내 잘못이야
Nothing should happen to me.
나한테는 아무 일도 일어나지 않아야 해
I just wanted to hide at home
그냥 집에 숨고 싶었어
In the end they
결국 그들은
There is no way to understand me
나를 이해할 길이 없어
you see me
당신은 나를 본다
Why am I saying this?
왜 이런 말을 하는 걸까요?
still
그래도
you don't understand either
너도 이해 못 해
I'm sorry ma'am
미안해요 부인
Slaves are stupid and don't understand anything.
노예는 멍청하고 아무것도 이해하지 못합니다.
you are not stupid to understand
당신은 이해하는 바보가 아니다
But no one understands
하지만 누구도 이해하지 못해요
I was so careless.
내가 너무 부주의했어
Because I trust adults...
나는 어른들을 믿기 때문에 ......
Ahead of the last ancestral rites
마지막 조상제사를 앞두고
she found nothing
그녀는 아무것도 찾지 못했다
I thought I could sit comfortably and relax.
편하게 앉아서 쉴 수 있을 것 같았는데
After this experience
이 경험 이후
That could be seen as a wake-up call to me.
그것은 나에게 경각심을 불러일으키는 신호라고 볼 수 있습니다.
Some things aren't as simple as you think
어떤 것들은 생각보다 간단하지 않아요
It's better to rely on yourself than on anyone else
누구보다 자신에게 의지하는 것이 낫다
Stop
멈추다
Someone is doing housework in the lab.
누군가가 연구실에서 집안일을 하고 있습니다.
You don't have to do this
이렇게 할 필요는 없습니다
Then I can't stay here in vain
그렇다면 나는 여기서 헛되이 머물 수 없다
until now
지금까지
What did you find out?
무엇을 알아냈나요?
I said it all
내가 다 말했어
This matter has nothing to do with A Qian.
이 문제는 A Qian과 관련이 없습니다.
Does my uncle not trust himself or me?
삼촌은 자신 도, 나도 믿지 않는 걸까 ?
Otherwise, why do we continue to highlight this issue?
그렇지 않다면 왜 이 문제를 계속해서 강조합니까?
south wind
남풍
-Uncle -Nowadays, we will hire more people day and night.
-삼촌 -요즘에는 밤낮으로 사람을 더 고용하겠습니다.
- A patrolman is watching me. - What's going on?
- 순찰대원이 저를 감시하고 있어요 - 무슨 일이에요?
I'm worried because there's an uninvited guest.
초대받지 않은 손님이 있어서 걱정이에요
Maybe the Ge family will take action again.
어쩌면 Ge 가족이 다시 조치를 취할 수도 있습니다.
Ge family?
Ge 가족?
It's not because too many fake perfumes have been made before.
이전에 가짜 향수를 너무 많이 만들어서가 아닙니다.
Did you tell your uncle to report to an official for sealing?
삼촌에게 봉인을 위해 공무원에게 보고하라고 했나?
How dare they appear after so many years ?
그토록 오랜 세월이 흐른 뒤에 어떻게 감히 그들이 나타날 수 있을까요 ?
It's hard to tell if a fish has slipped through the net and is on the verge of death.
그물을 빠져나가 죽을 지경인 물고기가 있다고 말하기는 어렵습니다.
I think you'd better be careful.
조심하시는 게 좋을 것 같아요
yes
예
Why did the eldest lady wake up so early today?
오늘 큰아줌마는 왜 이렇게 일찍 일어났나요?
I can not sleep
잠이 안 와요
I just woke up early.
방금 일찍 일어났어요.
By the way, go and organize the books in my store.
그런데 가서 내 가게에 있는 장부를 정리 좀 해라.
This Zhongzhai has all kinds of ledgers.
이 Zhongzhai에는 모든 종류의 장부가 있습니다.
But let’s look for Deacon Ji and Mother Lee.
그런데 지 집사님과 리 어머니님을 찾아보겠습니다.
I guess I'll have to ask when I look at the ledger later .
나중에 장부를 볼 때 물어봐야 할 것 같아요.
Is the eldest lady going to start learning housekeeping?
큰아줌마가 살림을 배우기 시작할 건가요?
Learn more
더 알아보기
The more it can be used for me
나에게 더 많이 사용될 수 있을수록
What is written in this book?
이 책에는 어떤 내용이 적혀 있나요?
oldest woman
가장 나이 많은 여자
Your trousseau store
당신의 트루소 매장
I don't know if it's small
작은지는 모르겠는데
My uncle said it earlier
삼촌이 아까 말했지
The eldest wife's dowry need not be kept in a public account.
큰 부인의 지참금은 공개 계좌에 보관할 필요가 없습니다.
A grown woman takes care of it herself.
다 큰 아주머니가 직접 챙겨주신다.
If there is a lack of manpower
인력이 부족하다면
Can you recommend one or two?
한두 가지만 추천해 주실 수 있나요?
The uncle doesn't want to interfere with his eldest wife's dowry.
삼촌은 큰 부인의 지참금을 방해하고 싶지 않습니다.
in this case
이 경우
If we divorce in the future
만약 우리가 미래에 이혼한다면
Just bring this coin and the store with you ‥
이 동전과 상점을 가지고 오시면 됩니다 ‥
You're wasting the maid's time.
가정부의 시간을 낭비하고 있습니다.
Let me explain about this store.
이 가게에 대해 설명해 드리겠습니다.
- If you have anything to do, please come first - OK
- 할 일 있으면 먼저 와주세요 - OK
The eldest lady and younger siblings will leave first.
그 큰 아줌마, 동생들이 먼저 떠날 거예요.
Madam, what do you say now?
부인, 지금은 어떻게 말씀하시나요?
It's getting more and more ugly, right?
점점 더 보기 흉해지죠?
But fortunately
하지만 다행스럽게도
Finally, you are willing to take on stewardship.
마침내 당신은 청지기 직분을 맡을 의향이 있습니다.
Like this
이런 식으로
Du Guan and his wife
두관과 그의 아내
Even if I feel at ease
마음이 편해지더라도
I am not interested in housework
나는 집안일에 관심이 없다
Learning this is for yourself in the future
이것을 배우는 것은 미래에 당신 자신을 위한 것입니다
You don't have to depend on anyone
누구에게도 의지할 필요 없어
Madam, look at this first.
부인, 먼저 이것 좀 보세요
uncle
삼촌
Teacher, are you going to the eldest lady’s yard?
선생님, 큰아줌마 마당에 가시나요?
Why are you telling me to go to my eldest aunt’s yard?
왜 그렇게 나한테 큰아줌마 마당에 가라고 하는 거야?
Even my men heard the news.
내 부하들도 그 소식을 들었어
Recently, I can't sleep or eat, so my eldest aunt is taking over the office work.
최근에는 잠도 못 자고 밥도 못 먹고 큰아줌마가 사무를 떠맡고 있다.
Sir, would you like to go and say hello?
선생님, 가서 인사하시겠습니까?
I don't want to hear anything like this from you again.
앞으로는 너한테 이런 소리 다시는 듣고 싶지 않아
If you have a bad nose
코가 심하다면
His subordinates deserve to die.
부하들은 죽어 마땅하다
WHO?
WHO?
it's me
나야
who are you?
누구세요?
how
어떻게
Don't you remember my voice?
내 목소리 기억 안 나?
Quickly chase me and go there
빨리 쫓아와 거기로 가
Hurry up and take a good look
서둘러, 잘 찾아봐
-fast -long
-빠른 -긴
Linglong
링롱
If you want to live
살고 싶다면
You'd better be quiet
조용히 하는 게 좋을 거야
The strong man visited the shepherd's house in the middle of the night.
그 힘센 사람은 한밤중에 목자의 집을 방문했습니다.
What is the point?
점은 무엇인가?
Use this place when you are hiding for a while
잠시 숨어있을 때 이곳을 이용하세요
Just wait and be patient.
그냥 기다려 인내심을 가지세요
I'll go out if there's no one outside.
밖에 사람 없으면 나갈게요
Honey, did you just call me?
자기야, 방금 나한테 전화했어?
- If you want to take one more hostage - girl
- 한 명 더 인질로 잡혀가고 싶다면 - 소녀
- You could have asked her to come in - Girl.
- 그녀에게 들어오라고 요청할 수도 있었죠
- What's the problem? -okay
- 무슨 문제 있어? -괜찮은
Just because it was too noisy outside right now.
단지 지금 밖이 너무 시끄러웠기 때문이에요
I would like to ask you to come and give me some instructions.
나는 당신이 와서 나에게 몇 가지 지시를 해주기를 요청하고 싶습니다.
He said officers and soldiers outside are now hunting down informers.
지금 밖에 있는 장교들과 군인들이 밀고자를 사냥하고 있다고 말했습니다.
So I got a little upset.
그래서 좀 난리가 났어요
I'll tell you now
이제 말해줄게
Are you hurt?
당신은 다쳤나요?
Inside the third drawer of the bookshelf
책장 세번째 서랍 안쪽
Jindao powder to stop bleeding and relieve pain
출혈을 멈추고 통증을 완화시키는 진다오 분말
Take it and try it yourself
직접 가져가서 사용해 보세요
Aren't you afraid of me?
당신은 나를 두려워하지 않습니까?
Because the strong man's journey has nothing to do with the Mu family,
강한 남자의 여행은 무 가문과는 아무런 관련이 없기 때문에,
Then help yourself
그럼 스스로 도와주세요
you are a woman's family
당신은 여자의 가족입니다
Are you really that sure about me?
너 정말 나에 대해 그렇게 확신하는 거야?
Be careful when you go out later
나중에 나갈때 조심하세요
Don't let anyone find you
다른 사람이 당신을 발견하지 못하게 하세요
It put the Mu family in trouble.
Mu 가족을 곤경에 빠뜨렸습니다.
Mujia
무지아
Such a coincidence
이런 우연이
how
어떻게
You were kicked out and then hid here again?
쫓겨났다가 또 여기에 숨었다고?
It seems truly unforgettable.
정말 잊혀지지 않는 것 같아요.
Please make me remember even now
지금도 나를 기억하게 해주세요
This is not my place
여긴 내 자리가 아니야
I have to hide, don't bother me
숨어야 해 귀찮게 하지 마
Because this place is not yours
이곳은 당신의 것이 아니기 때문에
Then do you want to come with me?
그럼 나랑 같이 갈래?
Do we know each other well?
우리는 서로를 잘 알고 있나요?
I once had a parrot
한때 앵무새를 키웠던 적이 있어요
You are like that too.
당신도 그것과 비슷해요
Are you sane?
제정신이에요?
Come with me. I will help you investigate your father's case.
나와 함께 가세요. 아버지 사건 조사를 도와드릴게요
Do you know about my father’s case?
우리 아버지 사건에 대해 아시나요?
Not long ago , there was a big uproar in Hwangseong City .
얼마 전 황성시에서는 큰 소란이 일었습니다 .
Who doesn't know?
누가 모르나요?
who are you?
누구세요?
Want to know?
알고 싶어요?
Then follow me and I'll tell you
그럼 나를 따라오면 말해줄게
I saw it these days
요즘 봤어요
No one in this Zhongzhai wants to believe what you say
이 Zhongzhai의 어느 누구도 당신의 말을 믿고 싶어하지 않습니다
You're trapped here but helpless
넌 여기에 갇혀있지만 무력해
There will be no results
결과가 없을 겁니다
as long as you follow me
당신이 나를 따라다니는 한
We can definitely help you turn the case around.
사건을 뒤집는 데 확실히 도움을 드릴 수 있어요
Why are you helping me?
왜 나를 돕는 거죠?
Think of it as repaying the favor of saving your life.
생명을 구한 은혜에 보답하는 것이라고 생각하십시오.
how?
어떻게?
Why should I trust you?
내가 왜 당신을 믿어야합니까?
'Cause I'm the only one who believes in you now
지금 당신을 믿는 사람은 나뿐이니까
The daring maniac dared to break into the servant's house at night.
대담한 미치광이는 밤에 감히 종의 집에 침입했습니다.
great
좋아요
remember this revenge
이 복수를 기억해
A notification has already been sent today.
오늘 이미 알림이 전송되었습니다.
I'll come pick you up publicly in 15 days.
보름 뒤에 공개적으로 데리러 올게요
muyao
무야오
- Mu Yao - Please find me
- 무야오 - 나를 찾아주세요
yes
예
Stay here and don't let the thief come back.
여기 남아서 도둑이 돌아오지 못하게 하라
Where did you go?
어디 갔다?
-There - quickly.
-저기 - 빨리
green bamboo
녹색 대나무
Why don't we go see what the noise is outside?
밖에 시끄러운 게 뭔지 보러 가는 게 어때요?
yes
예
Madam, your uncle is here.
부인, 삼촌이 오셨어요
uncle
삼촌
The weather is still cold, so be careful not to catch a cold.
날씨가 아직 추운데 감기조심하세요
Is your yard okay?
당신의 마당은 괜찮나요?
I just heard a lot of noise outside.
방금 밖에서 소란스러운 소리가 많이 들렸어요
What happen?
무슨 일이에요?
A thief suddenly came and dared to break into the servant's house at night.
갑자기 찾아온 도둑이 밤에 감히 종의 집에 침입했다.
It was Mu Yao who discovered the traces of the thief.
도둑의 흔적을 발견한 것은 무야오였다.
I fell and lost consciousness.
쓰러져 의식을 잃었다
what's the problem?
뭐가 문제 야?
How dare someone be so arrogant?
어떻게 감히 사람이 그렇게 오만할 수 있나요?
When I just came to see you
지금 막 보러 왔을 때
I noticed that there were very few people in your yard.
나는 당신의 마당에 사람이 거의 없다는 것을 알았습니다.
It's not peaceful at home these days
요즘 집이 평화롭지 않아요
I'll visit Jidong tomorrow.
내일은 지동을 찾아갈게요
please give me more guards
경비병을 더 주세요
There is no need for that.
그럴 필요는 없다
Okay, I'll send someone to find the maid tomorrow.
좋아요, 내일 가정부를 찾을 사람을 보내겠습니다.
You don't have to worry too much about the ancestor worship ceremony held on a full moon .
보름달에 열리는 조상숭배식은 크게 걱정하지 않으셔도 됩니다 .
i am always there
나는 항상 거기에 있어요
you were always weak
넌 늘 약했어
If you're tired
피곤하다면
just say
그냥 말해
Thank you for remembering, sir.
기억해주셔서 감사합니다 선생님
I'm so tired from mobilizing the army today.
오늘 군대 동원하느라 너무 피곤하다
Uncle, go back early and rest.
삼촌, 일찍 돌아가서 쉬세요.
Do you regret marrying Zhongzhai?
중자이와 결혼한 것을 후회하시나요?
What does this mean?
이게 무슨 말이에요?
I used to be drunk
나 예전에 술에 취해 있었어
So I accidentally missed your reputation
그래서 난 실수로 너의 평판을 놓쳤어
I thought you didn't want to marry me
당신이 나와 결혼하고 싶지 않은 줄 알았는데
But on my birthday...
그런데 내 생일에는 ......
I still love my uncle
나는 아직도 삼촌을 사랑하지만
But you can't accept him as yours like you used to
하지만 예전처럼 그를 네 것으로 받아들일 수는 없어
That's because I love him so much
그건 바로 내가 그 사람을 너무 사랑하기 때문이야
Then I really understood
그제서야 난 정말 이해하게 됐어
If that person is happy
그 사람이 행복하다면
I am willing to do anything.
나는 무엇이든 할 의향이 있다
Akian
아 키안
In the end I can't help you
결국 나는 당신을 도울 수 없습니다
The day it was my uncle's birthday
삼촌 생일이던 날
What I said was just......
내가 말한 것은 단지 ......
Just saying something inadvertently
그냥 무심코 하는 말
You don't have to worry, sir.
걱정하지 않으셔도 됩니다, 선생님.
no
아니요
I know these words have been hidden in your heart for a long time
이 말이 오랫동안 마음 속에 숨겨졌을 거라는 걸 알아요
So I wanted to use today as a time to express my feelings.
그래서 오늘 하루를 내 마음을 표현하는 시간으로 삼고 싶었어요.
I've been avoiding seeing you all these years.
나는 그동안 당신을 만나는 것을 피했습니다.
I thought to myself for a long time
오랫동안 혼자 생각했어요
This is a mistake I made when I was drunk
이건 내가 술취해서 저지른 실수야
I must admit
내가 인정해야만한다
Akian
아 키안
I will never let you down again from now on
앞으로는 다시는 널 실망시키지 않을게
What should I say to you?
내가 너한테 뭐라고 말해야 해?
It's not your fault at all
그건 전혀 네 잘못이 아니야
uncle
삼촌
I know what you're trying to say.
네가 무슨 말을 하려는지 알 겠어
this time
이번에는
I'm busy studying the ledger
난 장부를 공부하느라 바빠
And what to prepare for ancestral rites
그리고 조상제사를 위해 준비해야 할 것들
I'm so busy I feel dizzy
너무 바빠서 어지러움
Why don't you try something?
뭔가 좀 해보는 게 어때?
Wait until ancestor worship is over.
조상숭배가 끝날 때까지 기다리세요
Let's sit down and talk
앉아서 얘기하자
Why can't I say it now?
왜 지금은 말할 수 없나요?
what
무엇
It cannot be explained clearly in a few words.
몇 마디 말로는 명확하게 설명할 수 없다.
During this period, I don't have time to talk to you‥
이 기간 동안 나는 당신과 이야기할 시간이 없습니다 ‥
Be open and honest.
개방적이고 정직하십시오.
i hope you understand
나는 당신이 이해하기를 바랍니다
great
좋아요
Then it's up to you
그렇다면 그것은 당신에게 달려 있습니다
Okay, you can go find the manager tomorrow.
알았어, 내일 매니저 찾으러 가도 돼
Bring whoever you want
원하는 사람 데려오세요
yes ma'am
네, 부인
what are you doing? There are no rules at all.
뭐하는 거야? 규칙이 전혀 없어요.
I'm sorry, Sister Qianzhi.
미안해요, Qianzhi 자매님
sorry
죄송합니다
oldest woman
가장 나이 많은 여자
What's wrong with her?
그녀에게 무슨 문제가 있나?
It's normal for women to have emotions
여자들이 감정을 갖는 것은 정상이다
I can't be so generous.
그렇게 관대할 수가 없어요
Now that I think about it, today is really scary.
그러고 보니 오늘은 정말 무섭다.
I don’t know who was so bold and dared to break into Zhongzhai.
누가 그렇게 대담하고 감히 Zhongzhai에 침입했는지 모르겠습니다.
i know
알아요
Madam, you didn’t go out today.
부인, 오늘은 안 나가셨어요
How do I know?
어떻게 알 수 있나요?
Do you trust the person who broke in today?
오늘 침입한 사람을 믿으시나요?
Would you take the initiative to come to me in a few months?
몇 달 후에 솔선해서 나에게 오시겠어요?
Madam, please rest early.
부인, 일찍 쉬세요.
I'm finally waiting for you
드디어 당신을 기다리고 있어요
Mu Yao's fan number 3
무야오의 팬 No.3
don't disappoint me
나를 실망시키지 마세요
subordinate meets master
부하가 주인을 만났다
How was the check?
수표는 어땠나요?
person the owner is investigating
주인이 조사하고 있는 사람
It is currently located in Zhongzhai, Huangcheng City.
현재 황청시 중자이(Zhongzhai)에 있습니다.
Choosing?
중택?
The owner of Zhongzhai
중자이의 주인
Isn't this the same guy who once won by himself?
한때 혼자서 이겼던 그 사람이 아닌가?
Is this Jong-Ye-Ran sold in the south?
남쪽에서 장사하는 종예란인가?
exactly
정확히
in this case
이 경우
I would like to meet him for a moment.
나는 그를 잠시 만나고 싶습니다.
owner
소유자
Previously, the affairs of the Mu family were extremely secretive.
이전에는 무 가문의 업무가 극도로 비밀스러웠습니다.
Outsiders shouldn't know
외부인은 몰라야 해
The owner has nothing to worry about.
주인은 걱정할 게 없어요.
Moreover, in three months, you will be invited to a perfume tasting event.
게다가 3개월 후면 향수 시음회에 초대받는 날이 된다 .
at this point
이 시점에서
Master, you better not go to Huangcheng again.
스승님, 다시는 황청에 가지 않는 것이 좋습니다.
To prevent the conflict from getting bigger like last time
지난번처럼 분쟁이 더 커지지 않도록
Are you teaching me how to do something?
나한테 뭔가 하는 법을 가르쳐주고 있는 거야?
The subordinates dare
부하들은 감히
Before the feast
향연을 앞두고
I want to give a big gift to the Zhong family.
나는 종 가족에게 큰 선물을 주고 싶다
What about the old family masters?
옛 가족의 주인은 어떻습니까?
There is no need to inform your father in advance.
아버지에게 미리 알릴 필요가 없습니다.
After everything is done
모든 작업이 완료된 후
i will satisfy him
나는 그를 만족시킬 것이다
continued
계속되는
Thanks for watching
시청 해주셔서 감사합니다